Contact

kgibbs6283@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kimberlygibbsrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Nursing Leadership

Certifications

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Kimberly Gibbs, BSN, RN, CMSRN

VP of Nursing at Larksfield Place Retirement Communities, Inc. Goddard, Kansas

Summary

Experienced Nursing Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Innovation Management, Analytical Skills, Microsoft Word, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Healthcare Management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Wichita State University.

Experience

Larksfield Place Retirement Communities, Inc. 1 year 6 months

VP of Nursing June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Wichita, Kansas

Clinical Director Home Health and Hospice February 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months) Wichita, Kansas

Wesley Medical Center

5 years 11 months

Nurse Manager February 2016 - January 2019 (3 years)

Wichita, Kansas

Nurse Manager Ortho/Spine

Assistant Nurse Manager May 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 10 months) Wichita, Kansas

Staff Nurse

March 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Page 1 of 2

Wichita, Kansas

Homestead Health Center

10 months

Certified Medication Aide November 2010 - April 2011 (6 months)

Wichita, Kansas Area

Certified Nursing Assistant
July 2010 - November 2010 (5 months)

Wichita, Kansas Area

Celebrity Cruises, Inc.
Customer Service Representative
July 2001 - October 2006 (5 years 4 months)
Wichita, Kansas Area

Provide service and support to prospective and existing clients on products and services provided by Celebrity Cruises.

Service reservations and fulfill client needs to ensure client satisfaction.

Education

Wichita State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012)